<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sản phẩm &#8211; Epic Store </title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/myproject/wordpress/cua-hang/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../index.html</link>
	<description>Choose Your Game, Choose Your Way</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 15:07:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>CSGO : SÚNG LỤC MÔ HÌNH KIM LOẠI DESERT EAGLE (LỤC BẠC)</title>
		<link>./../../product/csgo-sung-luc-mo-hinh-kim-loai-desert-eagle-luc-bac/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/csgo-sung-luc-mo-hinh-kim-loai-desert-eagle-luc-bac/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 07:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=325</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[– Mô hình súng lục Desert Eagle được làm bằng <strong>kim loại và sơn tĩnh điện,tỷ lệ 1:1</strong> so với súng thật (23cm x 12cm).

– Sản phẩm chỉ là mô hình và <strong>KHÔNG BẮN ĐƯỢC.</strong>

– Mô hình có thể kéo đạn và bóp cò,có trọng lượng gần 1kg,cầm rất nặng tay.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[– Mô hình súng lục Desert Eagle được làm bằng <strong>kim loại và sơn tĩnh điện,tỷ lệ 1:1</strong> so với súng thật (23cm x 12cm).

– Sản phẩm chỉ là mô hình và <strong>KHÔNG BẮN ĐƯỢC.</strong>

– Mô hình có thể kéo đạn và bóp cò,có trọng lượng gần 1kg,cầm rất nặng tay.]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/csgo-sung-luc-mo-hinh-kim-loai-desert-eagle-luc-bac/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CSGO: DAO CAO SU M9 BAYONET (BLACK KNIFE)</title>
		<link>./../../product/csgo-dao-cao-su-m9-bayonet-black-knife/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/csgo-dao-cao-su-m9-bayonet-black-knife/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 07:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/csgo-dao-cao-su-m9-bayonet-black-knife/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CSGO: Súng AK47</title>
		<link>./../../product/csgo-sung-ak47/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/csgo-sung-ak47/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Đây là mẫu súng đồ chơi AK47 tỷ lệ 1:1 (85cm) thực sự,mặc dù trên thị trường có rất nhiều mẫu súng đồ chơi AK47 nhưng đa phần chỉ là 75cm trở xuống.
Sản phẩm có độ chi tiết cực cao,giống súng thật tới 95%,rất phù hợp để quay phim,chụp ảnh,sưu tầm,trưng bày,…
Súng sử dụng được đạn thạch,đạn nhựa,đạn cao su cỡ 6-7mm.
Bắn theo cơ chế lên đạn,bắn từng viên,gài đạn vào vỏ súng,khi lên đạn vỏ đạn sẽ văng ra ngoài như súng thật.
Vỏ súng được làm bằng nhựa cao cấp ABS-PP (Nhựa chuyên dùng để làm vỏ xe máy,oto) nên rất bền.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[Đây là mẫu súng đồ chơi AK47 tỷ lệ 1:1 (85cm) thực sự,mặc dù trên thị trường có rất nhiều mẫu súng đồ chơi AK47 nhưng đa phần chỉ là 75cm trở xuống.
Sản phẩm có độ chi tiết cực cao,giống súng thật tới 95%,rất phù hợp để quay phim,chụp ảnh,sưu tầm,trưng bày,…
Súng sử dụng được đạn thạch,đạn nhựa,đạn cao su cỡ 6-7mm.
Bắn theo cơ chế lên đạn,bắn từng viên,gài đạn vào vỏ súng,khi lên đạn vỏ đạn sẽ văng ra ngoài như súng thật.
Vỏ súng được làm bằng nhựa cao cấp ABS-PP (Nhựa chuyên dùng để làm vỏ xe máy,oto) nên rất bền.]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/csgo-sung-ak47/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CSGO: Súng AWP ASIIMOV</title>
		<link>./../../product/csgo-sung-awp-asiimov/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/csgo-sung-awp-asiimov/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 04:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Là mẫu súng AWM bắn cơ đạn thạch cao cấp nhất hiện tại,cả về thiết kế chi tiết đến từng con ốc,cho tới lực bắn rất mạnh,tầm xa lên tới 20met
Chất liệu nhựa nilon cao cấp cực bền,láng mịn,trọng lượng lớn hơn hẳn dòng súng chất liệu nhựa thông thường,tổng trọng lượng tính cả hộp lên tới 5kg.
Súng có thể tháo-lắp ráp như súng thật,kích thước 1:1 (140cm)]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[Là mẫu súng AWM bắn cơ đạn thạch cao cấp nhất hiện tại,cả về thiết kế chi tiết đến từng con ốc,cho tới lực bắn rất mạnh,tầm xa lên tới 20met
Chất liệu nhựa nilon cao cấp cực bền,láng mịn,trọng lượng lớn hơn hẳn dòng súng chất liệu nhựa thông thường,tổng trọng lượng tính cả hộp lên tới 5kg.
Súng có thể tháo-lắp ráp như súng thật,kích thước 1:1 (140cm)]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/csgo-sung-awp-asiimov/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Store Summer Sale 2021</title>
		<link>./../../product/epic-store-summer-sale-2021/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/epic-store-summer-sale-2021/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/epic-store-summer-sale-2021/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rust &#8211; Instruments Pack</title>
		<link>./../../product/rust-instruments-pack/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/rust-instruments-pack/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<br />
<b>Warning</b>:  mysqli_query(): (HY000/1036): Table 'C:\xampp\tmp\#sql435c_20cf_10.MAI' is read only in <b>C:\xampp\htdocs\myproject\wordpress\wp-includes\wp-db.php</b> on line <b>2056</b><br />
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[VỀ NỘI DUNG NÀY Reveal your inner musician in the Instrument Pack for Rust &#8211; a collection of 10 new musical instruments! Lay down a beat with the Drum Kit, belt out a tune on the Piano and become popular with your friends with the Cowbell! These new instruments use a new range of notes [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ NỘI DUNG NÀY</h2>
<p>Reveal your inner musician in the Instrument Pack for Rust &#8211; a collection of 10 new musical instruments!</p>
<p>Lay down a beat with the Drum Kit, belt out a tune on the Piano and become popular with your friends with the Cowbell! These new instruments use a new range of notes letting you play a variety of music. Announce your presence while raiding with a trumpet or entertain your team with the new Jerry Can Guitar on long boat rides.</p>
<p>Got a MIDI compatible keyboard or device? You can take your musical skills to the next level by plugging it in and playing the in-game instruments. Impress your friends!</p>
<p>The pack includes:</p>
<ul class="bb_ul">
<li>Wheelbarrow Piano</li>
<li>Junkyard Drum Kit</li>
<li>Xylobones</li>
<li>Plumber&#8217;s Trumpet</li>
<li>Sousaphone</li>
<li>Cowbell</li>
<li>Canbourine</li>
<li>Jerry Can Guitar</li>
<li>Shovel Bass</li>
<li>Pan Flute</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/rust-instruments-pack/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Forest</title>
		<link>./../../product/the-forest/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/the-forest/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>As the lone survivor of a passenger jet crash, you find yourself in a mysterious forest battling to stay alive against a society of cannibalistic mutants.</p>
<p>Build, explore, survive in this terrifying first person survival horror simulator.</p>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2>
<p>Enter a living, breathing world, where every tree and plant can be chopped down. Below ground explore a vast network of caves and underground lakes.</p>
<ul class="bb_ul">
<li>Chop down trees to build a camp, or start a fire to keep warm. Scavenge food to keep yourself from starving.</li>
<li>Build a small shelter or a large ocean side fortress. Lay traps and defences to keep a safe perimeter.</li>
<li>Explore and build during the day. Defend your base at night. Craft weapons and tools. Bunker down during the evening or bring the fight directly to the enemy.</li>
<li>Defend yourself against a clan of genetic mutant enemies that have beliefs, families, morals and that appear almost human.</li>
<li>Use stealth to evade enemies, or engage them directly with crude weapons built from sticks and stones.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/the-forest/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Crew™ 2</title>
		<link>./../../product/the-crew-2/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/the-crew-2/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>Play The CREW® 2 full game for free for 4 hours by downloading the trial!</p>
<p>The newest iteration in the revolutionary franchise, The Crew® 2 captures the thrill of the American motorsports spirit in one of the most exhilarating open worlds ever created. Welcome to Motornation, a huge, varied, action-packed, and beautiful playground built for motorsports throughout the entire US of A. Enjoy unrestrained exploration on ground, sea, and sky. From coast to coast, street and pro racers, off-road explorers, and freestylers gather and compete in all kinds of disciplines. Join them in high-octane contests and share every glorious moment with the world.</p>
<p>The Crew® 2 gives you the chance to showcase your skills and rise as a multi-skilled motorsports champion.</p>
<p>FEATURES<br />
WELCOME TO MOTORNATION – TAKE THE CHALLENGE TO THE GROUND, SEA, AND SKY<br />
Push boundaries and take on new experiences in iconic locations. Fly and spin through fog and clouds above the snowcapped Rocky Mountains, burn rubber in the backstreets of New York City, sweep through the Mississippi River, and explore every inch of the Grand Canyon. Driving your dream hypercar, riding some of the most iconic American bikes, and taking control of the swiftest aerobatic planes and powerboats: opportunities for fun and challenges are limitless in a fully redesigned USA.</p>
<p>SWITCH INSTANTLY BETWEEN VEHICLES &amp; ENJOY A 100% SEAMLESS EXPERIENCE<br />
The Crew® 2 is about open world freedom behind the wheel of your favorite rides. Shift from one to another with just a push of a button using the Fast Fav feature and experience the full potential of this huge and seamless open world. Cruising through L.A in your dream hypercar, switch to the swiftest aerobatic plane to rise above the skyscrapers and enjoy stunning perspectives over Hollywood, then swap it for a slick powerboat as you reach the coastline, landing smoothly on the Pacific ocean: opportunities for fun and challenges are limitless.</p>
<p>BE THE CHAMPION YOU WANT TO BE<br />
Join four different motorsports families from around the country: street and pro racers, off-road experts, and freestylers. They’ll hook you up with new rides, and they’ll introduce you to their own unique motorsports culture and set of disciplines. Through competitions and chance encounters, find and hone your personal style, collect and customize your dream rides, show them off in your HQ, and make your mark on the entire US motorsports scene.</p>
<p>SHARE AND SHINE IN A CONNECTED WORLD<br />
The world of The Crew® 2 is fueled by the need to share your personal accomplishments and unique moments with friends and others – break records and be a pioneer! Every time you achieve something, it will be saved as a new challenge for other players, while you will be encouraged to surpass the feats of others. Capture and share all of your best moments with the press of a button.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/the-crew-2/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GTA Grand Theft Auto V: Premium Online Edition</title>
		<link>./../../product/gta-grand-theft-auto-v-premium-online-edition/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/gta-grand-theft-auto-v-premium-online-edition/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<br />
<b>Warning</b>:  mysqli_query(): (HY000/1036): Table 'C:\xampp\tmp\#sql435c_20cf_17.MAI' is read only in <b>C:\xampp\htdocs\myproject\wordpress\wp-includes\wp-db.php</b> on line <b>2056</b><br />
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>When a young street hustler, a retired bank robber and a terrifying psychopath find themselves entangled with some of the most frightening and deranged elements of the criminal underworld, the U.S. government and the entertainment industry, they must pull off a series of dangerous heists to survive in a ruthless city in which they can trust nobody, least of all each other.</p>
<p>Grand Theft Auto V for PC offers players the option to explore the award-winning world of Los Santos and Blaine County in resolutions of up to 4k and beyond, as well as the chance to experience the game running at 60 frames per second.</p>
<p>The game offers players a huge range of PC-specific customization options, including over 25 separate configurable settings for texture quality, shaders, tessellation, anti-aliasing and more, as well as support and extensive customization for mouse and keyboard controls. Additional options include a population density slider to control car and pedestrian traffic, as well as dual and triple monitor support, 3D compatibility, and plug-and-play controller support.</p>
<p>Grand Theft Auto V for PC also includes Grand Theft Auto Online, with support for 30 players and two spectators. Grand Theft Auto Online for PC will include all existing gameplay upgrades and Rockstar-created content released since the launch of Grand Theft Auto Online, including Heists and Adversary modes.</p>
<p>The PC version of Grand Theft Auto V and Grand Theft Auto Online features First Person Mode, giving players the chance to explore the incredibly detailed world of Los Santos and Blaine County in an entirely new way.</p>
<p>Grand Theft Auto V for PC also brings the debut of the Rockstar Editor, a powerful suite of creative tools to quickly and easily capture, edit and share game footage from within Grand Theft Auto V and Grand Theft Auto Online. The Rockstar Editor’s Director Mode allows players the ability to stage their own scenes using prominent story characters, pedestrians, and even animals to bring their vision to life. Along with advanced camera manipulation and editing effects including fast and slow motion, and an array of camera filters, players can add their own music using songs from GTAV radio stations, or dynamically control the intensity of the game’s score. Completed videos can be uploaded directly from the Rockstar Editor to YouTube and the Rockstar Games Social Club for easy sharing.</p>
<p>Soundtrack artists The Alchemist and Oh No return as hosts of the new radio station, The Lab FM. The station features new and exclusive music from the production duo based on and inspired by the game’s original soundtrack. Collaborating guest artists include Earl Sweatshirt, Freddie Gibbs, Little Dragon, Killer Mike, Sam Herring from Future Islands, and more. Players can also discover Los Santos and Blaine County while enjoying their own music through Self Radio, a new radio station that will host player-created custom soundtracks.</p>
<p>Special access content requires Rockstar Games Social Club account. Visit <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=http://rockstargames.com/v/bonuscontent" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://rockstargames.com/v/bonuscontent</a> for details</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/gta-grand-theft-auto-v-premium-online-edition/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Counter-Strike: Global Prime Status Upgrade</title>
		<link>./../../product/counter-strike-global-prime-status-upgrade/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../product/counter-strike-global-prime-status-upgrade/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="list-title">
<div class="fontSize-title">Chi tiết sản phẩm</div>
</div>
<div class="description-container">
<p dir="ltr">Cũng giống như các phiên bản trước đó trong dòng game,<strong> </strong><em>Global Offensive</em> là một game bắn súng góc nhìn thứ nhất nối mạng dựa trên mục tiêu. Mỗi người chơi sẽ tham gia vào một trong hai phe khủng bố hoặc đội chống khủng bố và cố gắng để hoàn thành mục tiêu hoặc loại bỏ đội đối phương. Trò chơi hoạt động trong một hiệp ngắn (2 phút trong Competitive Mode) kết thúc khi tất cả người chơi ở một phe chết hoặc mục tiêu của đội đó được hoàn tất. Đối với hầu hết chế độ game, một khi người chơi chết đi, họ phải chờ đợi cho đến khi kết thúc lượt đi để hồi sinh. Người chơi mua vũ khí và trang bị vào đầu mỗi hiệp với tiền thưởng dựa trên hiệu suất họ đạt được ở vòng đấu trước đó. Hoàn thành mục tiêu hoặc tiêu diệt kẻ thù kiếm được nhiều tiền trong khi những hành động tiêu cực, như giết chết một đồng đội hoặc con tin, sẽ làm trừ đi số tiền thưởng của 1 hiệp chơi. Ngoài ra, khi kết thúc một hiệp tất cả người chơi đều nhận được một số tiền, với những người chơi trong đội chiến thắng thì nhận được nhiều hơn đáng kể so với đội thua.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Counter Strike: Global Offensive</em> còn bổ sung thêm các loại vũ khí và trang bị mới chưa từng thấy trong phiên bản trước, đáng chú ý nhất là bom lửa cho mỗi bên (Molotov cho khủng bố và lựu đạn gây cháy cho phe chống khủng bố), sẽ tạm thời gây ra một ngọn lửa bao trùm một khu vực nhỏ, gây sát thương cho bất cứ ai đi qua. <em>Global Offensive</em><strong> </strong>hỗ trợ việc tổ chức các trận đấu và xếp đầu bảng cho tất cả các chế độ chơi trực tuyến do Steam cung cấp. Dịch vụ trực tuyến được cung cấp đưa ra khả năng lọc theo chế độ game, bản đồ và một hệ thống bạn bè do Steam xây dựng nên. Valve còn sử dụng bộ công cụ chống gian lận Valve Anti-Cheat, có thể tự động loại bỏ và cấm người chơi sử dụng cheat ra khỏi mạng trực tuyến Valve. Để phù hợp với người chơi với những cấp độ kỹ năng tương tự, nhằm giúp người chơi trải nghiệm game một cách thú vị Valve sử dụng rank</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Q&amp;A:</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Q: Đây là tài khoản Counter-Strike (Acc Counter-Strike)?</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">A: Đây là sản phẩm CDKey kích hoạt bản quyền game <strong>Counter-Strike</strong>.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Q: Làm thế nào để có tài khoản Counter-Strike (Acc Counter-Strike)?</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">A: Tài khoản <strong>Counter-Strike</strong> chính là tài khoản Steam. Bạn có thể tạo tài khoản Steam dễ và miễn phí tại <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/join/?&amp;snr=1_60_4__62" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><u>ĐÂY</u></a>. Hướng dẫn tạo tài khoản bạn có thể tham khảo tại <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TNoHgjFu7J0&amp;feature=youtu.be" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><u>ĐÂY</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Q: Sau khi có tài khoản làm thế nào để chơi game?</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">A: Sau khi bạn đã tạo được tài khoản theo hướng dẫn bên trên, bạn chỉ cần mua sản phẩm <strong>Counter-Strike</strong> này. Sau đó, bạn sẽ nhận game theo hướng dẫn sau: <a href="https://divineshop.vn/huong-dan-nhan-game-steam-moi" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><u>https://divineshop.vn/huong-dan-nhan-game-steam-moi</u></a>. Tài khoản của bạn sẽ được kích hoạt bản quyền game <strong>Counter-Strike</strong> và tiến hành cài đặt bình thường sau đó bắt đầu trải nghiệm game.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Q: Sau khi mua sản phẩm game Counter-Strike ở máy này thì sang máy khác có chơi được không?</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">A: Có. Khi mua sản phẩm game là bạn mua cho tài khoản nên khi sang máy khác bạn chỉ cần đăng nhập tài khoản và cài đặt game là có thể chơi được như bình thường.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../product/counter-strike-global-prime-status-upgrade/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
