<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Adventure &#8211; Epic Store</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/myproject/wordpress/danh-muc-san-pham/adventure/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Một trang web mới sử dụng WordPress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:25:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Forest</title>
		<link>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-forest/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-forest/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>As the lone survivor of a passenger jet crash, you find yourself in a mysterious forest battling to stay alive against a society of cannibalistic mutants.</p>
<p>Build, explore, survive in this terrifying first person survival horror simulator.</p>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2>
<p>Enter a living, breathing world, where every tree and plant can be chopped down. Below ground explore a vast network of caves and underground lakes.</p>
<ul class="bb_ul">
<li>Chop down trees to build a camp, or start a fire to keep warm. Scavenge food to keep yourself from starving.</li>
<li>Build a small shelter or a large ocean side fortress. Lay traps and defences to keep a safe perimeter.</li>
<li>Explore and build during the day. Defend your base at night. Craft weapons and tools. Bunker down during the evening or bring the fight directly to the enemy.</li>
<li>Defend yourself against a clan of genetic mutant enemies that have beliefs, families, morals and that appear almost human.</li>
<li>Use stealth to evade enemies, or engage them directly with crude weapons built from sticks and stones.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-forest/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Crew™ 2</title>
		<link>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-crew-2/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-crew-2/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán bàng bằng <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong> hoặc mua siêu tốc với Mobile Banking. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận<strong> </strong><strong>50.000đ</strong> khi tải ví <strong>VNPAY </strong>và thanh toán tại <strong>DIVINE</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/tai-vi-vnpay-san-vang-ngay-cung-divine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Nhận Voucher mua thẻ cào <strong>50% </strong>khi thanh toán bằng thẻ <strong>ATM</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/nhan-voucher-50-khi-thanh-toan-bang-the-atm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>Play The CREW® 2 full game for free for 4 hours by downloading the trial!</p>
<p>The newest iteration in the revolutionary franchise, The Crew® 2 captures the thrill of the American motorsports spirit in one of the most exhilarating open worlds ever created. Welcome to Motornation, a huge, varied, action-packed, and beautiful playground built for motorsports throughout the entire US of A. Enjoy unrestrained exploration on ground, sea, and sky. From coast to coast, street and pro racers, off-road explorers, and freestylers gather and compete in all kinds of disciplines. Join them in high-octane contests and share every glorious moment with the world.</p>
<p>The Crew® 2 gives you the chance to showcase your skills and rise as a multi-skilled motorsports champion.</p>
<p>FEATURES<br />
WELCOME TO MOTORNATION – TAKE THE CHALLENGE TO THE GROUND, SEA, AND SKY<br />
Push boundaries and take on new experiences in iconic locations. Fly and spin through fog and clouds above the snowcapped Rocky Mountains, burn rubber in the backstreets of New York City, sweep through the Mississippi River, and explore every inch of the Grand Canyon. Driving your dream hypercar, riding some of the most iconic American bikes, and taking control of the swiftest aerobatic planes and powerboats: opportunities for fun and challenges are limitless in a fully redesigned USA.</p>
<p>SWITCH INSTANTLY BETWEEN VEHICLES &amp; ENJOY A 100% SEAMLESS EXPERIENCE<br />
The Crew® 2 is about open world freedom behind the wheel of your favorite rides. Shift from one to another with just a push of a button using the Fast Fav feature and experience the full potential of this huge and seamless open world. Cruising through L.A in your dream hypercar, switch to the swiftest aerobatic plane to rise above the skyscrapers and enjoy stunning perspectives over Hollywood, then swap it for a slick powerboat as you reach the coastline, landing smoothly on the Pacific ocean: opportunities for fun and challenges are limitless.</p>
<p>BE THE CHAMPION YOU WANT TO BE<br />
Join four different motorsports families from around the country: street and pro racers, off-road experts, and freestylers. They’ll hook you up with new rides, and they’ll introduce you to their own unique motorsports culture and set of disciplines. Through competitions and chance encounters, find and hone your personal style, collect and customize your dream rides, show them off in your HQ, and make your mark on the entire US motorsports scene.</p>
<p>SHARE AND SHINE IN A CONNECTED WORLD<br />
The world of The Crew® 2 is fueled by the need to share your personal accomplishments and unique moments with friends and others – break records and be a pioneer! Every time you achieve something, it will be saved as a new challenge for other players, while you will be encouraged to surpass the feats of others. Capture and share all of your best moments with the press of a button.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../sản%20phẩm/the-crew-2/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raft</title>
		<link>./../../../sản%20phẩm/raft/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../sản%20phẩm/raft/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán hoặc mua siêu tốc với <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Ưu đãi khủng <strong>30%</strong> lên tới <strong>50.000 đ</strong> khi sử dụng Ví VNPAY. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-khung-30-khi-su-dung-vi-vnpay#uu-dai-cho-nguoi-dung-vi-moi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p><strong>By yourself or with friends, your mission is to survive an epic oceanic adventure across<br />
a perilous sea! Gather debris to survive, expand your raft and be wary of the dangers of<br />
the ocean!</strong></p>
<p>Trapped on a small raft with nothing but a hook made of old plastic, players awake on a vast,<br />
blue ocean totally alone and with no land in sight! With a dry throat and an empty stomach,<br />
survival will not be easy!</p>
<p>Raft throws you and your friends into an epic adventure out on the big open sea, with the<br />
objective to stay alive, gather resources and build yourself a floating home worthy of<br />
survival.</p>
<p>Resources are tough to come by at sea: Players will have to make sure to catch whatever debris floats by using their trusty hook and when possible, scavenge the reefs beneath the waves and the islands above.<br />
However, thirst and hunger is not the only danger in the ocean… watch out for the man-<br />
eating shark determined to end your voyage!</p>
<p>Features:<br />
● Multiplayer! Survive by yourself or with friends in online co-op!<br />
● Hook! Use your hook to catch debris floating by.<br />
● Craft! Build survival equipment, weapons, crop plots and more to help you stay alive!<br />
● Build! Expand your raft from a simple wreckage to a buoyant mansion.<br />
● Research! Learn new things to craft in the research table.<br />
● Navigate! Sail your raft towards new places!<br />
● Dive! Drop anchor and explore the depths for more resources.<br />
● Fight! Defend your raft from the dangers of the ocean.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../sản%20phẩm/raft/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rust</title>
		<link>./../../../sản%20phẩm/rust/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../sản%20phẩm/rust/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán hoặc mua siêu tốc với <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Ưu đãi khủng <strong>30%</strong> lên tới <strong>50.000 đ</strong> khi sử dụng Ví VNPAY. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-khung-30-khi-su-dung-vi-vnpay#uu-dai-cho-nguoi-dung-vi-moi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>VỀ TRÒ CHƠI NÀY</h2>
<p>The only aim in Rust is to survive.</p>
<p>To do this you will need to overcome struggles such as hunger, thirst and cold. Build a fire. Build a shelter. Kill animals for meat. Protect yourself from other players, and kill them for meat. Create alliances with other players and form a town.</p>
<p>Do whatever it takes to survive.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../sản%20phẩm/rust/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Left 4 Dead 2</title>
		<link>./../../../sản%20phẩm/left-4-dead-2/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../sản%20phẩm/left-4-dead-2/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<h2>Khuyến mãi liên quan</h2>
<ul>
 	<li>Nhập mã <strong>DIVINE</strong><strong> </strong>giảm thêm <strong>10%</strong> tối đa 5.000đ khi thanh toán hoặc mua siêu tốc với <strong>VNPAY-QR</strong>. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-vnpay" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
 	<li>Ưu đãi khủng <strong>30%</strong> lên tới <strong>50.000 đ</strong> khi sử dụng Ví VNPAY. <a href="https://help.divineshop.vn/uu-dai/uu-dai-khung-30-khi-su-dung-vi-vnpay#uu-dai-cho-nguoi-dung-vi-moi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xem chi tiết</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lấy bối cảnh tận thế zombie, Left 4 Dead 2 (L4D2) là hậu bản đầy mong chờ của Left 4 Dead, trò chơi phối hợp số một đạt nhiều giải thưởng trong năm 2008.<br />
Trò chơi bắn súng kinh dị phối hợp góc nhìn thứ nhất này mang bạn và chiến hữu qua các thành phố, nghĩa địa và đầm lầy của Thâm Nam, từ Savannah tới New Orleans thông qua 5 chiến dịch mở rộng.<br />
Bạn sẽ chơi với tư cách 1 trong 4 người sống sót mới, được trang bị tận răng với dàn vũ khi kinh điển và cải tiến. Bên cạnh súng ống, giờ bạn cũng sẽ có thể trút sự giận dữ lên đám con bệnh với đủ loại vũ khí cận chiến tàn khốc, từ cưa máy cho đến rìu, và cả chiếc chảo cũng có thể gây chết người.<br />
Bạn sẽ thử dùng các vũ khí này để chống lại (hoặc nhập vai trong chế độ Đối Đầu) 3 con bệnh đặc biệt kinh khiếp và đáng gờm mới. Bạn sẽ đồng thời chạm trán với năm con bệnh lạ thường, bao gồm cả Mudmen đáng sợ.<br />
Đưa lối chơi đậm chất hành động, dữ dội của L4D lên một tầm cao mới là AI Director 2.0. Phiên bản cải tiến của Director giờ có thể thay đổi thời tiết bạn sẽ đối mặt và lộ trình bạn sẽ đi, bên cạnh khả năng điều chỉnh số lượng kẻ thù, hiệu ứng cùng âm thanh cho phù hợp với năng lực của bạn. L4D2 hứa hẹn đem đến một trải nghiệm thỏa mãn với nhiều thử thách độc lạ mỗi khi chơi, được tùy chỉnh cho phù hợp với phong cách chơi của bạn.</p>
<ul class="bb_ul">
<li>Trò chơi hành động phối hợp thế hệ mới từ nhà sáng tạo của Half-Life, Portal, Team Fortress và Counter-Strike.</li>
<li>Hơn 20 vũ khí &amp; trang bị mới, nổi bật là hơn 10 vũ khí cận chiến – rìu, máy cưa, chảo, gậy gộc – cho phép bạn tiếp cận gần hơn lũ zombie</li>
<li>Người sống sót mới. Cốt truyện mới. Câu thoại mới.</li>
<li>5 chiến dịch mở rộng cho các chế độ chơi phối hợp, Đối đầu và Sinh tồn.</li>
<li>Chế độ chơi nhiều người hoàn toàn mới.</li>
<li>Con bệnh lạ thường. 5 chiến dịch mới, mỗi cái có ít nhất một loại zombie bị nhiễm bệnh lạ thường mới chỉ dành riêng cho chiến dịch đó.</li>
<li>AI Director 2.0: Công nghệ tiên tiến hay còn gọi là AI Director định hình lối chơi độc đáo của L4D – tùy chỉnh số lượng kẻ thù, hiệu ứng và âm nhạc theo trình độ của người chơi. L4D2 giới thiệu AI Director 2.0, nay mở rộng khả năng của Director để tùy chỉnh thiết kế màn chơi, đồ vật, thời tiết và ánh sáng để phản ánh thời điểm khác nhau trong ngày.</li>
<li>Thống kê, xếp hạng và hệ thống phần thưởng khuyến khích lối chơi phối hợp</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../sản%20phẩm/left-4-dead-2/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
